

Professional and Extensive Full-stack, Blockchain Developer

Daniil Aslanov

Address : Kalnishevskogo 7, ap 1206 Kyiv Ukraine

Birthday: August 21, 1991

Phone: (+380) 960-929-493

GitHub: https://github.com/Topdev0104

Gmail: smartcode132@gmail.com

Job: Remote, Full-stack, Blockchain, Full-time, Any time zone

Front-end Developer

Full-stack Developer

Blockchain Engineer

Let me introduce myself

Welcome to my CV!

I am a full-stack developer who has 12+ years of experience.

Until now, I completed 20+ big projects and I delivered clients only satisfactory results.

I graduated from Kyiv National Economic University in Ukraine, and while I was in university, I loved computer programming because I had unusual hobby in computer engineering.

So, I studied computer program languages and algorithms very hard, and I showed to people my talents.

After graduating from university, I came to the United States and I joined Blue Eye Soft Corp company with my skills.

There, I had PHP and JavaScript projects first, working as a junior full-stack developer, and I completed the projects perfectly within a short time.

After 1 year, I became a senior full-stack developer and from then I developed frontend and backend of big projects.

After that, I joined several companies and I built many websites and web apps using such as JavaScript, React, Vue, Node.js, Express, PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter, Python, Django, ASP.NET.

Of course, I mastered almost all the JavaScript and PHP frameworks, but my strongest skills are React, Next, Vue, Nuxt, Node, Express, Laravel, Django.

Through the development of many projects, I had rich experience in web development and I found the most important development principles.

 Δ pixel perfect.

 Δ structured and optimized design of database.

 Δ smart and clean coding.

 Δ optimize of speed and code.

I always work with these principles and I update the project on GitHub per day.

Also, I can work in time what you want, and I can work 8+hours per day according to your requirements.

Only Perfect Result!!!

Thanks for visiting my CV.

My Blockchain Skills

Blockchain	95%
Solidity	100%
Smart Contract	95%
NFT Ecosystem	100%
Web3.js, Ether.js	100%
Truffle, Remix, Hardhat	100%
Cryptocurrency	90%

My Main Skills

\cup	
React, Redux, Next.js	100%
Angular	100%
Vue, Vuex, Nuxt.js	100%
TypeScript, JavaScript	100%
PHP, Laravel	100%
Django, Python	100%
ASP.NET, Node, Express	100%

Mastered programming languages

JavaScript PHP **TypeScript** Angular Node React **ASP.NET Express** Next.js Python Laravel Django Web3.js **NFT** Solidity Hardhat Truffle Remix

Work Experience

Front-end Developer at Blue Eye Soft Corp June 2013 ~ April 2016

- Implemented Single Page Application (SPA) architecture and client side MVC using Angular.js.
- Used Bootstrap features such as model objects, Tabs, Tooltips, Carousals throughout the application.
- Used Angular UI Grid directives such as filters, rootscope, childscope, modal, and template etc.
- Implemented components and wire-frames using cross-browser compatible CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query and AJAX, Angular.js.
- Implemented websites using Laravel Blade and Bootstrap and JavaScript and CSS.

Back-end Developer at AM-BITS August 2016 ~ February 2018

- Developed automated software which manages infrastructure without human intervention.
- Built multiple language website using Laravel with Vue.js frontend developer.
- Built shopping website using Django with React.js frontend developer.
- Implemented SEO(Search Engine Optimization) for several websites.
- PayPal integration using Laravel and Node.js.
- Web Scraping using Python.
- Web Hosting to Azure / CWP.

Full-stack Developer at Flytika July 2018 ~ April 2019

- Built Websites using React, Redux, Django, DynamoDB.
- Used ASP.NET Core and Python and Java.
- Developed an internal application that tracked the life of an order through a windows service and MongoDB.
- Improved SQL Server performance with stored procedure refactors and new constraints and indexes.
- Used GraphQL and REST API
- Development of Electron App and Used Next.js and Nuxt.js Web Hosting to AWS / Azure.

Full-stack Developer at WeTarget, July 2019 ~ Present

- Implemented pixel perfect frontend by design of client.
- Built websites using React & Django.
- Implemented SEO (Search Engine Optimization) to existing websites.
- Retrieved data from multiple, different storage APIs, using GraphQL.
- Payment Integration.
- Implemented Mail notification on several frameworks including React, Laravel, etc.
- Implemented Chat bot integration to several websites.
- Built big websites using React as frontend and Laravel as backend and MongoDB, MySQL as Database.
- Built United States website using Laravel Livewire and Vue.js.
- Web Hosting to AWS / CloudWays / cPanel.

Blockchain Engineer at Pstox, April 2020 ~ Present

- Explore Blockchain marketplace and research Blockchain technologies
- Generate NFT collection and metadata with client's layers and traits using hash-lip engine
- Build NFT minting website and make mint smart contract
- Build NFT marketplace with auction function
- Create and Mint business token and build staking token and claim rewards contract.
- Lay out the scale and scope of the software project and complete data structures and design patterns with team members
- Create project Git workflow and deployment automation on AWS,
 Firebase, Vercel
- Research design patterns, professional architecture, high-quality performance and security
- Build NFT minting site, NFT game site and NFT marketplace, and Decentralized Finance(Defi)

Education

Kyiv National Economic University

- Master of Computer Applications (MCA)
- July 2009 April 2013

Language Ukrainian Native or Bilingual Proficiency Russian Native or Bilingual Proficiency English Fluent

Typical Projects

Hamptons

(https://www.hamptonsrentals.com)

My client Neil wanted to me build your company site using Angular, ASP.NET, Bootstrap, etc. They are a real estate brokerage and they wanted to introduce their company via the internet. So, they decided that making a website that introduces their business and they hired me as a CTO.

I designed the database and structure of project and I completed using Angular 4 as frontend, ASP.NET as backend, PostgreSQL as database.

The company's business is real estate brokerage and they were able to introduce their company. Now, 10000+ users are using this site and users are keeping in touch by email and phone to discuss real estate problem with company. So, they are making more profits by introducing businesses to individual or company.

- JavaScript / Typescript
- HTML / Sass
- Bootstrap
- Angular 7
- ASP.NET
- Web scraping using Python
- PostgreSQL
- AWS cloud service

Pottorff (https://www.pottorff.com)

My client Linda wanted to me Build her website from her design using Laravel Livewire and Vue.js.

Pottorff is her company and she is in technical team of company. They made great louvers and dampers and they wanted to build a website to introduce their products.

So, she was finding a full-stack developer on behalf of the company and she hired me through the test.

This project includes complex Vue.js UI components and Laravel Livewire, axios, jsTree, MySQL database.

I had 3 team members and I built this site with my team.

As a team leader, I managed every part of project and I developed Product pages using jsTree, axios, etc. Also, I built all admin pages that require powerful security because I am the most excellent developer and leader.

Her company was able to introduce their business and they were able to keep in touch with many teams or individuals all around the world. So, they could produce a lot of products and get more profit.

- Vue.js / jsTree / Typescript
- Laravel Livewire
- MySQL
- Mail notification
- Web Hosting to Cloudways

Bitono (https://bitono.io)

My client Tam wanted me to build his betting site using Vue.js and Laravel with my creative idea from scratch.

The Structure and design were complicated and he wanted pixel perfect.

At first, he wanted me to build frontend so, I built frontend with my creative idea and his design using Vue.js UI components.

After that, he wanted to me implement some parts of Laravel backend and I implemented Paypal integration, stripe integration, Verification by using Email, Real time Notification by using Websocket, Chart API.

His team manages the betting system and a lot of people are playing the game. They are making more profit from management of game and their business are growing up more and more.

- Vue.js / Typescript
- Laravel
- Websocket
- Chart API
- Payment Integration
- Mail notification
- MySQL / MongoDB
- AWS cloud service

Spreadshirt

(https://www.spreadshirt.com)

My client Rafael wanted me to take part in updating their existing website. It is multiple language website and it included complex UI and several payment methods.

I built Men and Women pages using MERN(MongoDB, Express, React, Node) stack and PostgreSQL. The project uses Yarn 2 and follows the zero-install strategy.

Yarn performs a check-sum against the dependencies currently installed. It is a micro-frontend react application, with a Service Oriented Architecture. I used Emotion to style react components in JS, using emotions CSS prop with the object styles syntax.

The company was able to update the site on time and acquire 100,000+ users. The company was able to manage the business on a global scale and they were able to have many online agencies. So, they can advertise and sell many products on the online stores and they made a lot of profits.

- React/ Typescript
- Websocket
- Atomic Design
- Node.js / Express
- MySQL / MongoDB
- AWS cloud service / Lambda function

Ovolo (https://ovologroup.com)

My client Noha wanted me to build a hotel introduction and booking system website using React, Gatsby, Django.

It includes React Material UI, Redux, Mail notification, Payment integration, etc. The project uses Yarn 2 and follows the zero-install strategy. Yarn performs a check-sum against the dependencies currently installed. I built the frontend using React Material UI, Redux, Gatsby from his design, and I combined to backend with axios.

The company was able to start business on time and acquire 3000+ users. Nowadays, many customers book hotel and pay them via site. so, they are making \$1500000+ profits per year and they are providing blast to many users.

- React/ Redux / Gatsby
- Django
- DynamoDB
- Mail notification
- Payment integration
- AWS cloud service